hello we are setting off today's episode
with a rather special prank so something
happened okay it's been the hermitcraft
stream day today and basically what
happened was ren decided to tag me but
he forgot about his special requirement
which was he had to use an ender pearl
so what we're doing
is we're gonna set up a trap for the
next person on stream and that person is
good times with scar
so
we've set up this little hole and we've
got a little plan so what we've got is
we've made a little hole through the
concorp thing but we need to make it
seem like there's something down there
oh
oh oh oh oh he's here he's here he's
here he's here
there's nothing there's not enough down
there to coax him in there's there's
gotta be something
uh he's he's right here
ah he's escaping
no no no no he's delayed he's in
quickly ran where are you
go go go go go go go go go go go
[Music]
did he get him
no
get him
yeah yes
he got got
oh my goodness
oh that happened far too quickly i
wasn't ready i wasn't even done
explaining it
okay
it worked okay
[Laughter]
i trapped scar in
i trapped scar in this hole
i open it up ran through the end of
purlin oh what a what a tag team that
was scar was escaping so i jumped in and
knocked him down
and then an endermite came out of
nowhere from his ender pearl and killed
what a start to the episode it's been a
while since we've seen what's going on
in tag
oh scar scar didn't even know what just
hit him he had no idea what was going on
i just i i love it do you know what my
favorite thing about this whole thing
was the plan worked exactly as i planned
almost to the t because i was like if i
put a hole here scar is 100 percent
going to look down it and then i'm
gonna
hit him in
and then ren swoops in the only thing i
didn't count on was scar making his way
up and rent falling behind we weren't
ready it happened all too quickly far
too quickly
and now it's just the cleanup time we
only prank if we're gonna clean up
afterwards this is the concorp ship
after all
oh that was so brilliant i just oh that
oh okay so we're all cleaned up now
let's just fix up this boat and we can
replace a little bit of the water and
the job done
we have another successful tag and i'm
just glad that it's not me because ren
originally tagged me and i he just
walked up to me and tagged me i was like
nah dude we gotta we're gonna do this
properly so just because he didn't
follow his ender pearl rule it meant
that the tag was void because we follow
the rules here in hermitcraft
mostly
so good times with scar is officially
tagged
he probably feels so betrayed right now
so the stream day continues i think i
might join one of the stream days one
day
and
now
we have made major
major sales in the shop over here
look at all how many is that 32 diamonds
33 diamonds
60 a stack of diamonds
and the little extra as well
that's nearly a stack and a half of
diamonds not bad for an hour's grind i
have no idea how many diamonds i'd get
if i was to grind normally but that's
not bad we need to restock immediately
because quartz sells like crazy i think
that building had a lot to do with it
but quartz is something that everyone
kind of wants
i think this is the first time i'm
putting a load of profit in here so it
feels good because i've been spending
more than i'm making
okay so let's restock with all this
quartz i didn't collect quite as much as
before but this should
last well it'll last until one of one of
the hermits turns up and buys it all
because that seems to be how it goes
okay that's nearly a double chest full
that's the most i can manage at the
moment maybe i should stock up on some
other things like sand and gravel so
because i've been away i haven't
actually had a chance to work too much
on my base but as you can see these
these are doing pretty well i think
these do a lot to the build i just need
to add one more and i've got it
symmetrical on both sides
but that's not actually what i want to
do today i actually want to make the
shop for
this machine and i read loads of
comments and i think i prefer the name
stash for cash
so that's going to be the name of the
shop whether that's the name of this
machine i'm not sure
whether that's the name of this machine
i'm not entirely sure but stash for cash
is definitely the name of the shop and
then maybe this is the mumbo something
or other
i'm not entirely set on it but we'll get
there in the end so now
it's time to go ahead and build this
little shop
somewhere over in the shopping district
to try and sell the use of this machine
for three stacks of diamonds because you
just saw we sold all of that nether
quartz it took me an hour's grind to get
all of it for a stack and a half one
click of that button three stacks of
diamonds money money money
so i've got all of the wood that i could
possibly need to make this shop i'm
going to keep it simple elegant and
small because after all i'm not actually
selling anything in it it's just like an
information place but before we go i
actually want to do something i need to
send a message to mumbo to ask him if he
wants to go and play golf with the boys
all right golf with me and iskall from g
let's go and send that in the mail
hopefully he hasn't got too many eggs in
his system
i actually recent there off it goes i
recently checked it and there's still a
lot of chickens stuck in the system i
think i might actually have to go and
yeah
i don't think these guys are gonna move
i'm gonna have to go and purge the
system i think because
these guys aren't actually making their
way i cleared out mumbo's inbox a while
ago but it's clear at the moment wait if
it's clear at the moment why hasn't
oh there it is
wait what's going on here
something's not right here
the water is just piling it straight up
i think his system's not working okay so
i've gone and put the i've actually just
gone and put this in here
um something's definitely not right with
the system because like the items just
come out and they just flop straight
over
no idea what's going on there i think
something went haywire with this water
i think mumbo needs to fix it let's just
head on down and see if we can purge it
can i get down here if i if i use
rockets enough can i get down
get inside oh my goodness i can't
believe that that worked
all right
let's clear them out ah
no no
i didn't think about
this bit
oh yes
that is so speedy okay that was
magnificent all right let's get rid of
these guys because
if all of these are left here they're
just there's just going to be infinite
chickens forever we're going to have to
clear them out
admittedly i didn't think that they
would get that stuck in this could you
imagine calling around a plumber because
you've got chickens in your pipe work
only on the hermitcraft server there's a
surprisingly large amount of chicken
still
it doesn't end
i'm unblocking this because i actually
want mumbo to check his mail if there's
constantly eggs and stuff in there he's
just never gonna check the mail we're
almost back at the base
last little bit
64 chickens
it's quite a lot okay i think we're
ready to go and make the stash for cash
shop now but we actually need to go and
find a nice place for it to be made now
the shopping district's getting kind of
full
so we really need to think about this
there's a nice space there nice space
there or we could put it on something
that's already existing i don't really
want to put it on the pickle man i did
think about maybe making a mustache here
and you have to fly in the mouth hmm
i wonder if that's a good idea or not
let me ask eggs in his eye zuma voyage
i don't really want to build it without
permission
but it could be really cool like imagine
that the mustache is it's not going to
look like mumbo's mustache because i
don't want people to get confused but it
is gonna be a mustache all the same so
it's kind of gonna go
over i don't know i don't know maybe i
could just make it standing on its own
there's a space here there's a space on
any of these i could make it even above
the stock exchange
it's open for debate really is
i think i'm just gonna make it here
nothing's really been built here it
doesn't seem to be reserved and it's not
gonna take up a huge amount of space so
let's just go for it shall we and i'm
thinking of making it out of spruce
planks
so yeah let's just go and do it
so i'm trying to get like a really full
shape so that it doesn't quite look like
anyone's mustache in the game currently
and you can't get confused and i was
actually thinking maybe i could put a
big red circle through the middle
to kind of show what it is it's gonna be
a very weird shop i've got to admit
but getting this shape completely right
is gonna be tough
as long as i can get one side finished
that's all i need because it's easy to
replicate after that i think that looks
pretty good actually i'm i'm impressed
i'm pretty happy with how that that's
all gone so it's not the biggest
mustache in the world but it is just
going to be a space to be able to put in
a couple of signs yeah i think that
could work just replicate that over one
more time and we are on to a winner
that is the main mustache done actually
that doesn't look too bad does it you
can definitely tell what it is i hope
actually should we go for a little fly
around because that's how everyone else
is going to view this
yep you can tell that that's a mustache
and that is the main thing
now the brilliant part of how this is
going to work as a shot because this on
its own is not quite enough so i've got
loads of dark oak here as well and a
bunch of black concrete and i'm going to
try and make a little mouth here
i don't know how it's going to look this
is completely experimental
but if i can get this right this is
going to be the entrance to the
shop itself
so
how do i do this i kind of want to make
him seem happy
i think the key would be to make a very
small mouth
let's see if we can do this
that's not even big enough for anyone to
get through
and it looks terrible this may not work
you know this might not work as a
concept
oh dear i didn't didn't plan on this
because my entire concept relied on the
fact that you could get inside the shop
yeah that looks really really weird i'm
not gonna lie but you could fly through
it i'm getting really good at flying i
gotta admit
now here's an idea so hear me out this
is gonna be the mouth you can actually
walk through it now but if i give the
entire mustache an outline
then
one block behind it it could look
completely normal to have that mouth
there
if this doesn't work then the entire
shop is
void and probably not gonna work too
well
okay let's take a little step back and
see what that looks like
and
yes
that actually works quite nicely it's
not quite symmetrical but
that does the trick
so now to create the effect of being
inside the mouth of this oh
i'm gonna have to maybe sacrifice some
of the mouth not entirely sure or maybe
i could put i'm gonna put red here i
don't actually have any red on me
unless i use netherrack here
that could oh it does actually look like
a tongue
that's actually really good uh hopefully
that works that was a bit of a
i only had another wreck on me so that
worked out really well
so
that actually that looks perfect
that looks so good with the nether rack
i can't believe how much that actually
looks like a tongue i've never thought
of using it that way
this is brilliant the only thing i can
think of actually is maybe what we do
is we move these because you can
actually see these so i'm thinking we
move these back one block
we can make that work i'm sure
so this is going to be the actual
entrance here you can't see it too much
from the outside but if i use enough
black blocks you should be able to see
it just fine
let's take a little step back to see our
handiwork
that works brilliantly absolutely
brilliantly i love this
this doesn't even need to be any eyes
although i can imagine someone will add
eyes at some point
all that has to be done now is a little
bit of covering up
quickly make this an encased shop so
that there's actually some space and
then we can work briefly on the interior
i'm really enjoying what this is right
now it does look absolutely silly which
is exactly what the mumbo mustache
remover is all about
i haven't really seen any interest from
the other hermits and that's a little
bit worrying i thought when i put my
video out about the mumbo's mustache
removal i thought that every hermit in
the world wanted to remove his mustache
but now i'm faced with the very real
possibility
that it's just me
it can't be just me right everyone
everyone wants to rip the mustache away
am i weird am i weird for wanting to
strip away the mustache of my fellow
hermits
i
that's normal right
i'm normal
there's not a lot of space in here but
remember this shop there's no point in
making it really really big because if
it was massive and people go inside and
it just says
well you know get in touch with gree and
then oh it's a bit of a waste of space
if you ask me so we're just going to
make something off to the side not not
too well it might stand out a little bit
but it's not going to take up too much
space
and hopefully we should get a few really
good laughs out of this
i don't think anyone's going to look too
closely at the back but i have a bad
habit of not finishing projects 100 and
then i just never get back to them so
this time we're not gonna do that
just the last little bit to do for this
exterior and it will be finished and
exterior is now officially finished i
believe
that took
not too long actually i'm surprised it
kind of nailed i kind of nailed it first
time i feel
let's go and take a little step back and
see what this looks like
oh
my goodness i love it i absolutely love
this let's go and fly around
so people flying around yeah they'll see
this mustache it even looks like it's a
mustache on this building i do want to
create just one more thing but ow
i do like the fact that you try and you
have to try and fly into the mouth which
i kind of like because i really enjoy
flying and then you can come up into
here now turning this into some sort of
meaningful interior
is not going to be easy
not going to be easy at all
i'm going to try and keep it as simple
as possible
i'm maybe not gonna
yeah i'm probably not gonna try and
spend too much time on this
uh at the end of the day all we're gonna
do here is send them to my base or you
know get them to get in contact with me
it only really needs to be small enough
to pass on a message you know
the main thing is putting something in
the shopping district itself because
i've learned that unless it's in the
shopping district people just aren't
going to see it all i need now is to go
and grab my red wool and we can finish
this up i'm thinking that red concrete
will actually look better so here i am
picking some poppies
i don't know how much i'm gonna get out
of this but yeah i need i need some red
dye i'm gonna make red concrete and
that's where i'm gonna make my big
circle with a line through it and that
should put the whole thing together
really really well
i just think the red on the concrete is
much more intense and that way we can
drag more attention
to the mustache itself
all right got my red concrete now i just
need to kind of
picture how this is going to go because
um it needs to be a big enough circle
but also it's probably going to come out
of the middle here i think the place to
start is up the top and then what we're
going to do is this is the middle here
so we want to make sure that the height
is just right
yep i think that might be the one the
only problem is there's a lot of red
going on in the background with this
rocket but hey that's definitely a red
circle and all i got to do now is
connect up these two
the only thing that i want to say about
this is it's not a perfect circle as the
line that goes through will not really
look like a line it's not going to be a
perfectly diagonal line
i think
that is pretty good i did make some
final alterations
but that seems to have done the trick
now if you want to go inside you kind of
have to fly in the hole
right there we go so this is all we need
now maybe just a smidging of light in
here would do the trick
and we got ourselves a nice space
it says welcome to stash for cash we'll
take away mumbo stash for your cash use
of the machine costs three stacks of
diamonds to use the machine get in touch
with green directly who will operate the
machine on your behalf
the machine will then translocate
mumbo's facial hair somewhere in the
hermitcraft server for someone to find
meanwhile our naked lipped friend will
feel a cold breeze on his face and feel
incomplete let's be honest we all want
to take away his mustache
green
bop that's it
it's done stash for cash is officially
open and that's basically it that's all
i needed to do put the book in there so
that there is something here in the
shopping district for people to find
and yeah that's that was it that was as
simple as that i'm very very happy with
how this has come out in the end so i
think that's pretty much where we're
going to leave today's episode we
finally made stash for cash and
hopefully we will get a few orders
for taking away mumbo's mustache we also
gave the tag to scar
and that was absolutely brilliant it had
me in stitches and we also de-clogged
the messaging system between me and
mumbo
alright thank you very much for watching
everyone and i will see you in the next
episode where hopefully ow we'll play
some golf
all right goodbye